http://www.quadrantsoftware.com/terms-and-conditions/

E-mail us or call 1-800-258-3399
Skip to content
Modernization, FoIP and Document Output Management Solutions for IBM i
For Quadrant Software Internet World Wide Web Sites
Quadrant Software LLC, its subsidiaries and affiliates (“Quadrant Software”) requires that all the visitors to our site(s) on the World Wide Web (the “Site”) adhere to the following rules and regulations. By accessing the Site you indicate your acknowledgment and acceptance of these terms and conditions.
1. LAWS AND REGULATIONS
User access to and use of the Site is subject to all applicable international, federal, state and local laws and regulations.
2. COPYRIGHT/TRADEMARKS
The trademarks, logos and service marks (“Marks”) displayed on the Site are the property of Quadrant Software and other parties. The FastFax(TM) and Formtastic(TM)trademarks are the property of Quadrant Software, LLC. Users are prohibited from using any Marks for any purpose including, but not limited to use as metatags on other pages or sites on the World Wide Web without the written permission of Quadrant Software or such third party which may own the Marks. All information and content including any software programs available on or through the Site (“Content”) is protected by copyright. Users are prohibited from modifying, copying, distributing, transmitting, displaying, publishing, selling, licensing, creating derivative works or using any Content available on or through the Site for commercial or public purposes.
3. HYPERLINKING
THIS SITE MAY PROVIDE A LINK TO OTHER SITES BY ALLOWING THE USER TO LEAVE THIS SITE TO ACCESS THIRD-PARTY MATERIAL OR BY BRINGING THE THIRD-PARTY MATERIAL INTO THIS SITE VIA “INVERSE” HYPERLINKS AND FRAMING TECHNOLOGY (A “LINKED SITE”). QUADRANT SOFTWARE HAS NO DISCRETION TO ALTER, UPDATE, OR CONTROL THE CONTENT ON A LINKED SITE. THE FACT THAT QUADRANT SOFTWARE HAS PROVIDED A LINK TO A SITE IS NOT AN ENDORSEMENT, AUTHORIZATION, SPONSORSHIP, OR AFFILIATION WITH RESPECT TO SUCH SITE, ITS OWNERS, OR ITS PROVIDERS. THERE ARE INHERENT RISKS IN RELYING UPON USING, OR RETRIEVING ANY INFORMATION FOUND ON THE INTERNET, AND QUADRANT SOFTWARE URGES YOU TO MAKE SURE YOU UNDERSTAND THESE RISKS BEFORE RELYING UPON, USING, OR RETRIEVING ANY SUCH INFORMATION ON A LINKED SITE.
4. NO WARRANTIES
ALL CONTENT, PRODUCTS, AND SERVICES ON THE SITE, OR OBTAINED FROM A WEBSITE TO WHICH THE SITE IS LINKED (A “LINKED SITE”) ARE PROVIDED TO YOU “AS IS” WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, SECURITY OR ACCURACY.
QUADRANT SOFTWARE DOES NOT ENDORSE AND IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR (A) THE ACCURACY OR RELIABILITY OF ANY OPINION, ADVICE OR STATEMENT MADE THROUGH THE SITE BY ANY PARTY OTHER THAN QUADRANT SOFTWARE, (B) ANY CONTENT PROVIDED ON LINKED SITES OR (C) THE CAPABILITIES OR RELIABILITY OF ANY PRODUCT OR SERVICE OBTAINED FROM A LINKED SITE.
OTHER THAN AS REQUIRED UNDER APPLICABLE CONSUMER PROTECTION LAW, UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCE WILL QUADRANT SOFTWARE BE LIABLE FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE CAUSED BY A USER’S RELIANCE ON INFORMATION OBTAINED THROUGH THE SITE OR A LINKED SITE, OR USER’S RELIANCE ON ANY PRODUCT OR SERVICE OBTAINED FROM A LINKED SITE. IT IS THE RESPONSIBILITY OF THE USER TO EVALUATE THE ACCURACY, COMPLETENESS OR USEFULNESS OF ANY OPINION, ADVICE OR OTHER CONTENT AVAILABLE THROUGH THE SITE, OR OBTAINED FROM A LINKED SITE. PLEASE SEEK THE ADVICE OF PROFESSIONALS, AS APPROPRIATE, REGARDING THE EVALUATION OF ANY SPECIFIC OPINION, ADVICE, PRODUCT, SERVICE, OR OTHER CONTENT.
5. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR USE OF THE SITE AND LINKED SITES
THE INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS AND DESCRIPTIONS OF SERVICES PUBLISHED ON THE SITE OR A LINKED SITE MAY INCLUDE INACCURACIES OR TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS, AND QUADRANT SOFTWARE SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIMS ANY LIABILITY FOR SUCH INACCURACIES OR ERRORS. QUADRANT SOFTWARE DOES NOT WARRANT OR REPRESENT THAT THE CONTENT ON THE SITE IS COMPLETE OR UP-TO-DATE. QUADRANT SOFTWARE IS UNDER NO OBLIGATION TO UPDATE ANY CONTENT ON THE SITE. QUADRANT SOFTWARE MAY CHANGE THE CONTENT ON THE SITE AT ANY TIME WITHOUT NOTICE. QUADRANT SOFTWARE MAY MAKE IMPROVEMENTS OR CHANGES TO THE SITE AT ANY TIME.
YOU AGREE THAT QUADRANT SOFTWARE, ITS AFFILIATES AND ANY OF THEIR RESPECTIVE OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, OR AGENTS WILL NOT BE LIABLE, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT, STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE, FOR ANY INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, INCIDENTAL OR INDIRECT DAMAGES (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION LOST PROFITS, COST OF PROCURING SUBSTITUTE SERVICE OR LOST OPPORTUNITY) ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OF THE SITE OR A LINKED SITE, OR WITH THE DELAY OR INABILITY TO USE THE SITE OR A LINKED SITE, EVEN IF QUADRANT SOFTWARE IS MADE AWARE OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. THIS LIMITATION ON LIABILITY INCLUDES, BUT IS NOT LIMITED TO, THE TRANSMISSION OF ANY VIRUSES WHICH MAY INFECT A USER’S EQUIPMENT, FAILURE OF MECHANICAL OR ELECTRONIC EQUIPMENT OR COMMUNICATION LINES, TELEPHONE OR OTHER INTERCONNECT PROBLEMS (e.g., YOU CANNOT ACCESS YOUR INTERNET SERVICE PROVIDER), UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS, THEFT, OPERATOR ERRORS, STRIKES OR OTHER LABOR PROBLEMS OR ANY FORCE MAJEURE. QUADRANT SOFTWARE CANNOT AND DOES NOT GUARANTEE CONTINUOUS, UNINTERRUPTED OR SECURE ACCESS TO THE WEB SITE.
6. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR SERVICES ARRANGED THROUGH THE SITE
YOU AGREE THAT QUADRANT SOFTWARE IS A MERE AGENT FOR THE PROVIDERS OF SERVICES AVAILABLE THROUGH THE SITE. ANY AND ALL CLAIMS REGARDING ANY FAILURE OR BREACH WITH RESPECT TO THE SERVICES OFFERED THROUGH THE SITE ARE LIMITED TO CLAIMS AGAINST ANY AND ALL SERVICE PROVIDERS. QUADRANT SOFTWARE HEREBY DISCLAIMS ANY LIABILITY, WHETHER BASED ON CONTRACT, TORT, STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION LIABILITY FOR ANY DIRECT, PUNITIVE, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, INCIDENTAL OUR INDIRECT DAMAGES, IN CONNECTION WITH THE GOODS OR SERVICES PROVIDED BY ANY CARRIER OR OTHER SUPPLIER THROUGH THE SITE, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION LIABILITY FOR ANY ACT, ERROR, OMISSION, INJURY, LOSS, ACCIDENT, DELAY OR IRREGULARITY WHICH MAY BE INCURRED THROUGH THE FAULT, NEGLIGENT OR OTHERWISE, OF SUCH CARRIER OR SUPPLIER AND YOU HEREBY EXONERATE QUADRANT SOFTWARE FROM ANY LIABILITY WITH RESPECT TO THE SAME.
7. CONFIDENTIALITY OF USER COMMUNICATIONS
Except as required by law and in accordance with the Quadrant Software Internet Privacy Statement. Quadrant Software will maintain the confidentiality of all user communications which contain personal user information and which are transmitted directly to Quadrant Software. Postings by a user on any message board or in any chat room will not be protected as confidential and Quadrant Software may use and provide information contained in any such postings (including any ideas, concepts, know-how or other intellectual property) to any of its parent company, subsidiaries and affiliates for any purpose whatsoever and as deemed appropriate by Quadrant Software. User should be aware that Linked Sites may contain confidentiality provisions that differ from the provisions provided herein. Quadrant Software is not responsible for such provisions, and expressly disclaims any and all liability related to such provisions.
8. LINKED INTERNET SITES
Quadrant Software prohibits caching, unauthorized hypertext links to the Site and the framing of any Content available through the Site. Quadrant Software reserves the right to disable any unauthorized links or frames and specifically disclaims any responsibility for the Content available on any other Internet sites linked to the Site. Access to any other Internet sites linked to the Site is at the user’s own risk. User should be aware that Linked Sites may contain rules and regulations, privacy provisions, confidentiality provisions, transmission of personal data provisions, and other provisions that differ from the provisions provided on the Site. Quadrant Software is not responsible for such provisions, and expressly disclaims any and all liability related to such provisions.
9. PRESS RELEASES
All press releases and other materials presented or released to the financial community that are contained on the Site were, to the best of Quadrant Software’ knowledge, timely and accurate when issued. However, the passage of time can render information stale, and you should not rely on the continued accuracy of any such material beyond the date of issuance. Quadrant Software has no responsibility to update any information contained in any such material. All viewers should carefully check the dates of issuance of the material contained in the Site.
10. POSTINGS
Quadrant Software is under no obligation to review any messages, information or content (“Postings”) posted on the Site by users and assumes no responsibility or liability relating to any such Postings. Notwithstanding the above, Quadrant Software may from time to time monitor the Postings on the Site and may decline to accept and/or remove any Postings that contain:
Any unlawful, harmful, threatening, abusive, harassing, defamatory, vulgar, obscene, profane, hateful, racially, ethnically or otherwise objectionable material of any kind, including, but not limited to, any material which encourages conduct that would constitute a criminal offense, give rise to civil liability or otherwise violate any applicable local, state, national or international law.
Advertisements or solicitations of any kind.
Messages posted by users impersonating others.
Personal information such as messages which state phone numbers, social security numbers, account numbers, addresses, or employer references.
Messages by non-spokesperson employees of Quadrant Software purporting to speak on behalf of Quadrant Software or containing confidential information or expressing opinions concerning Quadrant Software.
Messages that offer unauthorized downloads of any copyrighted or private information.
Multiple messages placed within individual folders by the same user restating the same point.
Chain letters of any kind.
11. TRANSMISSION OF PERSONAL DATA
User acknowledges and agrees that by providing Quadrant Software with any personal or proprietary user information through the Site, user consents to the transmission of such personal or proprietary user information over international borders as necessary for processing in accordance with Quadrant Software’ standard business practices. User should be aware that Linked Sites may contain transmission of personal data provisions that differ from the provisions provided herein. Quadrant Software is not responsible for such provisions, and expressly disclaims any and all liability related to such provisions.
12. CHANGES TO RULES AND REGULATIONS
Quadrant Software reserves the right to revise these Rules and Regulations at any time and users are deemed to be apprised of and bound by any changes to these Rules and Regulations.
13. VIOLATIONS OF RULES AND REGULATIONS
Quadrant Software reserves the right to seek all remedies available at law and in equity for violations of these Rules and Regulations, including the right to block access from a particular Internet address to the Site.
14. ACCESS TO PASSWORD PROTECTED/SECURE AREAS
Access to and use of password protected and/or secure areas of the Site is restricted to authorized users only. Unauthorized individuals attempting to access these areas of the Site may be subject to prosecution.
15. USE OF “COOKIE” FILE FEATURES
Quadrant Software reserves the right to store information on a user’s computer in the form of a “cookie” or similar file for purposes of modifying the Site to reflect users’ preferences. The Quadrant Software Internet Privacy Statement provides additional information regarding Quadrant Software’ use of cookies as well as procedures for disabling cookies.
16. DIGITAL MILLENNIUM COPYRIGHT ACT – NOTIFICATION TO QUADRANT SOFTWARE REGARDING ALLEGED COPYRIGHT INFRINGEMENT
Quadrant Software has registered an agent with the United States Copyright Office in accordance with the terms of the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (the “Act”) and avails itself of the protections under the Act. Quadrant Software reserves the right to remove any Content on the Site which allegedly infringes another person’s copyright. Notices to Quadrant Software regarding any alleged copyright infringement on the Site should be directed to Quadrant Software’s Legal Department at: 540 Myles Standish Boulevard, Taunton, MA (USA) 02780
17. JURISDICTION/GOVERNING LAW
Users of this Site agree to be governed by the laws of the Commonwealth of Massachusetts and the United States, including copyright laws, without regard to its conflict of laws rules or the United Nations Convention on the International Sale of Goods. Venue in the event of any suit, proceeding or claim will be in the state and federal courts located in Boston, Massachusetts (U.S.).
Schedule a livedemonstration
Contact Us+1-800-258-3399Email Us
Email Support
Solutions
Document Creation
Document Delivery
Payment Automation
Document Workflow
Copyright © 2020 Quadrant Software, All Rights Reserved     Quadrant Software | 124 Grove St. | Franklin, MA 02038 USA
Privacy Policy
Terms and Conditions
Sitemap
Trademark
